skattertech.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy | Skatter

Skatter Tech, Inc. (“Skatter Tech”) operates skatter.com (the, “Website”). It is Skatter Tech’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

## Website Visitors

Skatter Tech collects non-personal information that most modern web browsers and servers typically make available. These include, but are not limited to the browser type/version, default language, Internet Protocol (IP) address, Internet Service Provider, geographic location, referring domain, screen resolution, and the timestamp of each request. This anonymous information helps Skatter Tech better understand visitors, improve user experience, and combat spam. We may publish, release, or share non-personally-identifying information to feature usage trends of the Website. While the aforementioned collected information is considered non-personally-identifying, email addresses and IP addresses are stored for users who choose to post a comment.

## Personally-Identifying Information

Skatter Tech discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to its employees. Skatter Tech will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, Skatter Tech may disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Skatter Tech believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Skatter Tech, third parties, or the public at large. Skatter Tech will take all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Email Solicitation

If you have provided your email address to Skatter Tech, you will not receive emails from us unless you have granted permission to do so. Communication from Skatter Tech may not always offer a link to terminate future solicitation. Under those circumstances, please contact Skatter Tech to request termination of future email communication.

## Publishing Rights

If you send us a support request through the contact form or to a Skatter Tech email address, we reserve the right to publish the content of the request, in part or whole, to help us respond to your request or support other users. We will not publish potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information without your permission.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Skatter Tech uses cookies to help Skatter Tech identify and track visitors, their usage of the Website, and their website access preferences. Skatter Tech visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before accessing the Website. Certain features may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Advertisements

Ads that appear on the Website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Skatter Tech and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. If you do not wish to have third-party cookies placed in your browser, you may choose to use ad-blocking software to disable advertisements.

## Changes

Skatter Tech may change its Privacy Policy at any time in Skatter Tech’s sole discretion. Skatter Tech encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. A link to this “Privacy Policy” is provided at the bottom of each page. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

 **Change Log:**  
December 24, 2010 – New Terms & Conditions for Skatter Tech, Inc.
